Chanrith "Hong" Leatheng

Phone: (864)2793641 | Email: lhcr.workline@gmail.com

Portfolio Website: https://hong-webport.github.io/ | Github: https://github.com/Hong-webport

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/hong-leatheng-4aaa5b200/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Multi-skilled IT Professional, committed to lifelong learning with a love of solving problems, team collaborations and collective improvements. Skilled in Data Modeling, Analysis and Visualization using Python, Tableau, PowerBI and Splunk. Continue learning with machine learning, AI and statistics. Have experience in CyberSecurity, Data Analysis and Industry Automation.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Information Security Engineering Analyst- Wells Fargo

2021 - 2023:

Monitored and maintained six data warehouse centers, covering over 15,000 appliances with cloud software.

- Monitor and create daily and weekly data reports and visualization, data dashboards, and automated alerts in order to search, troubleshoot, restart, analyze, and fix inactive appliances, ensuring smooth operation and stability across the enterprise, with Splunk, Guardium and othe software.
- Extract, Transform and Load (ETL) relational databases of Oracle, MsSQL, and Linux servers.
- Installed patches and updated software versions to maintain a high level of security and kept updates with cloud structures. Participate in migrations to new software and decommissioning of legacy systems.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams across different time zones, adopting a Scrum and Agile mindset, to identify and resolve issues promptly.

System Integration Technician - Dollar Tree Distribution Center

2019 – 2020:

Integrated, installed, optimized, debugged, troubleshot, and repaired automation and robotic systems (Automatic Storage and Retrieval System) consisted of 150+ robots using diagnostics tools and problem-solving.

- Using data analysis along with a variety of diagnostics software and communication with operators, engineers and managers, I assisted in installing a massive fully-automated system, integrating them with previous semi-automated system, different software and hardwares such as printers, machine vision camera, and others.
- Training new operators, writing documentations, developed new processes for the benefits of the team.

Tech Scholar - Michelin North America

2017-2019:

Take part in preventive maintenance and other associated tasks including quality audits, documentations and writing work instructions. Often, participating in brainstorming sessions on improving the skills of our team, the effectiveness of our methods.

• Succeeded in reducing a significant amount of operational cost in the pneumatic system.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Data Management and Cloud Software: Microsoft PowerBI | Tableau | Splunk | IBM Security Guardium | Microsoft Azure | AWS | Tableau | SAP | Postgres | Linux | Mongdb

Programming Languages and Framework: Python | JavaScript | SQL | Window Scripting | Django | Bootstraps | D3 | Pandas | HTML | CSS | Excel VBA | RestAPI |

Industrial Automation: KUKA | ABB | TGW Stingrays | Siemens PLC | Allen-Bradley PLC | Staubli

EDUCATION:

Certificate of Completion in Data Sciences and Analysis:

Georgia Institute of Technology

Associate of Applied Science, AAS, in Mechatronics:

Spartanburg Community College

Bachelor of Professional Design:

Limkokwing University of Creative Technology

Industry Certifications and Others:

Microsoft Azure AZ-900 | Splunk Foundamentals II | Kuka Robots Kore Certification